Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
Ms. Frieren.
You're late.
You defeated Aura, didn't you?
Like a fairy tale
It's a sign the story has reached its end
Like a single passage taken from
A journey that was too long
Of the evil that once cast a shadow
Across this land
And the memories of the short journey
With the hero who defeated it
The story ends
And the hero goes to sleep
Leaving this land with
Days of peace and quiet
The passage of time heartlessly
Makes people forget
Even the tracks left behind by his life
Begin to rust
Just the same
Your words and wishes and courage
Are still inside of me
And they live on
We chose the same path
That's all it was supposed to be
Why is it that at some point
I wanted to understand the reason for
The tears that fall down my cheeks
Even now
If I retrace the journey we walked together
Even though you're not there
I know I'll be able to find it
I don't believe—
I can't believe this happened.
Let's go.
Wait. You don't need to run.
The graf said he'd pardon you.
It must have been a fierce battle,
but none of them are seriously damaged.
Thank you for treating the heroes
of the northern lands with respect.
I used to cast flashier spells,
but Himmel got mad at me.
I bet he did.
He was right to be angry. I'd be angry, too.
Mr. Himmel trained you well.
Don't say it like that.
I guess you're right, though.
This is a normal reaction.
What do you mean?
Don't worry about it.
Fern, Stark.
Good job defeating Lügner and his henchwoman.
I'm proud of you.
I'd be even more impressed
if you weren't so beat up, though.
This is normal for a warrior.
What does "normal" even mean?
You're covered in wounds.
See that they receive proper burials.
I'll escort our benefactors to the city.
Yes, milord.
Milord.
What is it?
Frieren.
I've never been as grateful to anyone
as I am to you today.
Frieren, I promised to reward you
in any way I could.
You requested the defensive
barrier grimoire by Flamme
that has been passed down
for generations in my family.
Are you sure this is what you want?
This grimoire...
It's fake.
Yes. The defensive barrier it describes
is nothing like our city's barrier,
whose spell is passed down by oral tradition.
I'm well aware of that, milord.
It's just my hobby.
I see.
Either way, you needn't use
such formal language.
From your perspective,
I must seem akin to an infant.
I suffered a bitter experience when
I first left to defeat the Demon King.
Come to think of it, Mr. Heiter
said that in the royal capital,
disrespecting nobility
is punishable by death.
Himmel and Eisen were nearly executed
for speaking casually to the king.
Remembering Himmel screaming
and crying takes me back.
Execution? That's extreme.
And speaking so casually to me
is a serious crime in this town, brat.
Sorry, old man.
I'm gonna break this
expensive-looking chair.
Th-The central lands sure
are barbaric, milord.
Seriously?
I've finished cutting the
trees in the backyard.
Thank you.
Well, you know, I only said that
so you'd escape.
In this town, you won't be thrown
in prison just for speaking casually.
Be at ease.
In that case...
Good news for you, Mr. Stark.
He's passed out.
I've told the townsfolk of Aura's defeat.
They all want to honor the heroes.
I ask that you take your time here.
He's floating.
It's not that big a deal.
The name that has protected me
Is being called by that soothing voice of yours
So that you won't close your eyes all alone
I'll embrace you
You joined your warm hands with mine
So I won't forget
Beyond the night, where it's full of flowers
It is where you are, a place I will return to
Split the swelling, unravel the darkness
So that the dream remains uncorrupted
To the blue path that never ends
I finished the shopping.
Shall we go, then?
You're leaving already, Frieren?
Graf Granat.
I'll see you to the gates.
Frieren, I hear you're traveling to Ende,
the farthest point north,
where the Demon King's castle is.
But currently, conditions on the
Northern Plateau aren't looking good.
Travel is restricted.
Even adventurers must be accompanied
by a first-class mage.
Then there should no problem
with Ms. Frieren by our side.
What's a first-class mage?
Ms. Frieren, you don't know?
It's a certification awarded by the
Continental Magic Association.
Certification?
I acquired mine in the
holy capital when we left.
See?
This is my third-class mage certificate.
Come to think of it, you did have
some business to take care of then.
Is this what certifications
look like these days?
Ms. Frieren, don't tell me you're
an uncertified underground mage.
Don't make it sound like
I'm some back-alley doctor.
The organizations that regulate
mages are constantly changing.
I can't be bothered obtaining
a new certification every time.
I doubt this holy emblem works anymore.
What is that antique?
Even I know about the
Continental Magic Association.
They've been around for over
half a century at the very least.
That's barely anything.
It's a hassle when they change their
standards of conduct so frequently.
In any case, we'll need to overcome
this problem before we continue.
I don't know the specifics,
but I believe there's a place
in the northern lands
where you can take the first-class exam.
The largest magical city in the
northern lands, Äußerst.
It's far beyond the Schwer Mountains.
You can follow the highway,
but it'll be a long journey.
Frieren, the house of Granat will
never forget what you've done for us.
Safe travels.
It's snowing.
It's almost winter.
The winters around here are bitter,
so be careful.
If you underestimate them, you'll die.
Is it really that dangerous?
Don't you know?
In the war against the Demon King's forces,
what do you think claimed the most lives?
It was the winters of the northern lands.
See? We're lost.
What are we going to do?
We're lost.
I can't believe we got lost before
even entering the Schwer Mountains.
Mr. Stark, wake up!
If you fall asleep, you'll die!
Have jumbo-berry specials
always been this small?
Who cares about that right now?
What should we do?
In these strong winds,
we can't transport him with magic.
He'd probably be blown away.
Then we'll have to carry him.
He's heavy.
Why is he so heavy?
You smell nice.
Can I leave him behind?
Bear it for now.
There should be an emergency shelter
at the foot of the mountains.
Isn't that information
eighty years out of date?
Are we going to be all right?
Good.
It's still being maintained regularly.
It seems like someone's inside.
Perhaps someone arrived before us.
We're going inside.
We'll freeze out here.
Good! Very good!
I'm starting to feel warmer!
Excuse the intrusion.
Ms. Frieren, we can't stay here.
Let's look for someplace else.
What? Why?
There's a pervert inside.
A pervert? That's awfully rude.
Let's go, Ms. Frieren.
Wait. Are you an elf?
It's been about 300 years since
I've met another of my kind.
I thought the elves had already died out.
So did I.
And thanks for the fire, miss.
Not at all.
I'm lucky I ran into a couple of mages.
The Goddess must have led you here.
I crossed the Schwer Mountains,
but this blizzard extinguished my coals.
I was keeping myself alive by doing
squats inside this freezing hut.
I see.
I'm not sure I understand.
I'm Kraft the Monk.
Frieren the Mage.
Fern, also a mage.
This is Mr. Stark the Warrior.
Anyway, Aureole, huh?
You're traveling to heaven, then?
Good on you for being so pious.
I'm not sure I totally believe it.
Ms. Frieren.
Mr. Stark is getting colder.
So warm and comfortable...
And that's one huge jumbo-berry special.
What happened to me?
We got caught in a blizzard, and then...
Who is this guy?
You're so noisy.
That's no way to thank someone
for warming you up with their body.
Their body?
You've got a nice body, old man.
Mr. Stark?
No, not like that.
I mean he's got a nice body
from training hard.
You must be really strong.
What's your name?
Kraft the Monk.
I've never heard of you.
But you must be a pretty famous monk, right?
Stark, rest here.
You two, help me bring in food supplies.
My wagon and cargo are nearby.
I'm really glad I met all of you.
We'll be able to use these frozen supplies.
Use as much as you'd like.
You've certainly stocked up.
Trying to cross the Schwer Mountains
in these conditions would be suicide.
We're stuck here for a while.
By the way, Frieren, do you know who I am?
Not at all.
I didn't think so.
I don't know the first thing
about you, either.
She's the mage from the party of heroes.
And before that?
What do you mean?
I mean that we're elves.
It's been nearly six months.
Thanks to all of you, we made it through
the long winter in the northern lands.
Take this.
Give it to Fern. She's a pious girl.
Must be because she was raised by a priest.
She never forgets to thank the Goddess.
Kraft, why do you believe in the Goddess?
You don't, do you?
Excluding during the age of mythology,
the Goddess of Creation hasn't shown herself
once in the long history of this world.
You're young. I used to think that way, too.
But now I believe in the Goddess
from the bottom of my heart.
No, I need her to exist.
Everyone who knew of my
righteous triumphs has died.
So when I die, I'll go to heaven
and the Goddess will praise me.
She'll say, "Well done, Kraft."
"You lived a fantastic life."
You understand that, Frieren.
It's too cruel for the path your life took
to not be remembered by anyone.
We've lived a long time to get to this point.
Kraft, that's just something we desire.
You're right.
Does that apply to heaven too, Frieren?
No matter.
Tell me about yourself,
and I'll tell you about myself.
If you don't believe in the Goddess,
then I'll praise you instead.
Are you surprised?
Yeah. I didn't think you'd fund the
reconstruction of this village's orphanage.
You don't beat around the bush, do you?
I was an orphan, too.
I'm sure the Goddess will praise me
for living a pure and proper life.
What are you talking about, you corrupt
priest? You're drinking right now.
Frieren.
Do you have someone to praise you?
Where did that come from?
You don't seem to believe in the Goddess,
so if you tell me about yourself,
I'll praise you instead.
I haven't done much with my life.
I haven't done anything praiseworthy.
Even though you're constantly
suppressing your mana?
To me, that seems like the
result of tremendous effort.
Something that would take
a lifetime to accomplish.
You noticed?
How many years have we
traveled together again?
It's not an interesting story.
I don't mind.
Besides, it sounds like something
useful to know for the future.
Why?
Perhaps a child of mine will become a mage.
I thought priests couldn't marry.
Why do so many strange
people serve the Goddess?
I'll pass. I've already had
someone else praise me.
I see. You have good friends, Frieren.
You should cherish them.
Actually, he's already...
He's in heaven now.
Then you'll see him again someday.
You're right.
I'm going this way.
Frieren, I doubt this is
the last time we'll meet.
I'll see you in a few centuries.
Take care, old man! I had fun!
Thank you for the pendant!
And you alright
Can you hear me
Trailing along deserted train tracks
Crying excessively
Wanting you to smile
I hold on to memories I'd like to keep fresh
There's something I'd like to tell you
With words more precious than a goodbye
Unremarkable yet special
See, things that couldn't have been
Seen if it weren't for these eyes
Why? They begin to overflow
So, if I were to be born again
I would surely choose this place once more
So, if we were to meet again
I'd never let you go, I'd choose the present
Even if no promises were made
Even if I'm lost in days of loneliness
Those tears will be alright,
dawn will surely break
I'm whispering our lullaby
for you to come back home
His pure white cape proves that he's
I'm a mild-mannered person,
but even I'm pissed off.
This village used to protect the Hero's Sword.
the strongest warrior in the village.
It's a replica.
They're a gift to honor warriors
who have worked hard.
Perv.
We're not warriors.
Don't tell the rest of the family.
He was a real hero.